Banker's birth was indeed a great moment
of joy for a parents grandparents uncles
and aunts proud papa anush was happy
super happy but he gets super worried
too he remembers his colleagues advice
being a father is a matter of great joy
but a great responsibility to look at
education for imagine the amount of
money you'll need to 23 years from now
look at inflation it's your duty to
provide for her how
idea anush quickly checks smart kid with
ICICI Pro Smart Life a market link ulip
plan specially designed to meet your
child's future needs and he invests just
5,000 rupees per month in the plan with
a policy term of 23 years in a few
years Papa uncle
proudly sends punu to the best school in
town without a worry of Hefty school
fees as he was already prepared as furi
grows into a beautiful smart and
confident young woman she has many
dreams to fulfill many new Skies to fly
anush was ready to support her dreams
with an investment that was growing with
boring Unos should the proud papa once
again he's happy that he took the right
decision at the right time his timely
investment in smart kid with ICI Pro
Smart Life ulip Plan paid off he can now
lean back and relax fully confident of
his daughter's future as the plan will
take care of her dreams and amb missions
even when he is not there anymore
[Music]
just like anos you can also secure your
child's future by investing in smart kid
with ICI Pro Smart Life buying smart kid
with ICI Pro Smart Life online is safe
secure and convenient it also comes with
the benefit of 1% discount on premium
allocation Char and what's more you can
enjoy tax benefits too start planning
for your child's future today visit
www.ollie.com